

NGUYỄN HOÀNG TUẨN KHANH

Front-End Website Developer

- 0866110231
- tuankhanhbf@gmail.com
- i https://www.facebook.com/profile.php? id=100027566643711
- District 8, Ho Chi Minh City
- **19/10/2000**
- nale



link gibhub:

https://github.com/TuanKhanh1910

Career goals

Learn more about web programming.

Specifically Front-End development. At the same time, learning more about the Backend

Skills

JAVASCRIPT

Github

HTML & CSS (SASS) & BOOTSTRAP

REACTJS & TAILWINDS & ANT DESIGN



Introduce myself

My name is Nguyen Hoang Tuan Khanh, 23 years old. After graduating from high school, I started learning German. After a year and a half I got my B1 from the Goethe-Institut. After I got my B1, I worked as a mentor for a German language center (10/2019 - 11/2020). Around November 2021 I got a German visa and flew to Germany. In Germany I studied auto mechanics but for a half year I felt that I was not suitable for this manual job(11/2021 - 5/2022). From the above two jobs, I have accumulated a lot of experience: team work, always on time at work, responsibility in work always comes first, and always have a spirit of learning. Then I returned to vietnam and started learning about web programming. After 9 months i started to do an internship at cybersoft for 4 months, during the internship i learned more skills about front-end



Education

CYBERSOFT ACADAMY

MARCH 27 - JULY 21

Major: Front-End Web Developer



Work experience

MENTOR

8/10/2019 - 10/11/2020

Trung tâm dạy tiếng Đức DSHi

Đã từng có kinh nghiệm trợ giảng 1 năm tiếng Đức cho trung tâm tiếng Đức.

MENTOR

27/3/2023 - 30/7/2023

Trung tâm đào tạo lập trình Cybersoft

Đã từng có kinh nghiệm trợ giảng nữa năm cho trung tâm đào tạo lập trình Cyrbersoft .



CERTIFICATIONS

2020 Bằng ngôn ngữ tiếng Đức B1

2023

Front-End Website Developer from Cybersoft Academy. During my internship here, I have accumulated a lot of experience. How to use libraries or frameworks, how to use git (git add, git commit, git push, git merge,..), how to work as a team to build a website



PORTFOLIO

STUDIOS WEBSITE:

- + Teamsize: 3
- + Responsibility: Development build HomePage, fix bugs, responsive, merge code from branches together
- + Link Demo: https://bcs-07-gr4-studious.vercel.app/
- + link Github: https://github.com/TuanKhanh1910/BCS07_gr4_Studious
- + Technology: HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap 4, Jquery, waypoints, countup js, owl carousel,qithub

SAMAR WEBSITE:

JQUERY

- + Teamsize: 1
- + Responsibility: make the whole website, build all the functionality in the website
- + Link Demo: https://bcs-07-khanh-samar.vercel.app/
- + Link Github: https://github.com/TuanKhanh1910/BCS07_Khanh_samar
- + Technology: HTML5, CSS3, Jquery, wowjs,, count up js, waypoints, owl carousel, github

MOVIE ĐẶT VÉ:

- + Teamsize: 1
- + Responsibility: make the whole website, build all the functionality in the website (book a ticket and show the information of the person who booked that ticket)
- + Link Demo: https://bcs-07-react-movie-khanh.vercel.app/
- + Link Github: https://github.com/TuanKhanh1910/BCS07_reactMovie_Khanh
- + Technology: ReactJS, react-redux,react-router-dom,axios,reduxjs/toolkit,github

SHOES WEBSITE:

- + Teamsize: 1
- + Responsibility :make the whole website, build all the functionality in the website (display all shoe products, and clicking on details will show the details of that shoe)
- + link Demo: https://bcs-07-capstone-khanh.vercel.app/
- + link Github: https://github.com/TuanKhanh1910/BCS07_ShoesReact_Khanh
- +Technology: ReactJS, CSS3, Bootstrap 4

AirB&B WEBSITE:

- + Teamsize: 3
- + Responsibility: build homepage (show all products), detail page for each product (which includes user reviews) and reponsive
- + Link Demo: https://cuoikhoafe.vercel.app/
- + Link Github: https://github.com/LePhamAnhTuan/cuoikhoafe
- + Technology: ReactJS, tailwindcss, reduxjs/toolkit,antd,axios,flowbite,formik,moment,react-router-dom,react-icons,react-lottie,react-redux